好的  现在扶好壁炉两侧
Okay, now holding sides of hearth in position,
啊  被纸片划到手了
Aw, I got a little paper cut.
哦  拜托  我最近都很少玩了
Oh, come on, I hardly ever get a chance to play anymore.
你个可怜的小家伙
you poor thing.
我应该事先跟你说清楚的
I should've mentioned this earlier.
周六晚上?
Saturday night?
可是我这周每天晚上都在加班
But I've been working late all week.
但我必须得去
But I have to go.
我们是一个团队
We play as a group.
所以  你看吧?
So, you see?
你个傻子
You're an idiot.
我是你的傻子
I'm your idiot.
圣诞礼物?
A Christmas gift?
你知道我不喜欢圣诞节啊
You know I don't enjoy Christmas.
唉  从哪里说起好呢?
Oh, where to begin?
长在屋子里的树
Trees indoors.
人人都知道袜子应该是一双一双的
Everyone knows socks belong in pas.
谁穿一只袜子呀?
Who uses one sock?
一条腿的海盗?
Pirate with a peg leg?
哦  一个卷轴
Oh, a scroll.
我喜欢卷轴
I like scrolls.
他们是我第三最爱的
They're my third
好的
Okay,
不好意思打扰一下你们的小游戏
I don't mean to interrupt your little game,
我的角色已经死了
My character died.
当然  我明白的
Sure. I get it.
为什么要支持一个朋友呢?
Why support a friend?
你没见过我的店吗?
Have you seen my store?
我根本不打算说任何幼稚的话
I wasn't going to say anything so juvenile.
很好  你会怎么做呢?
Great. what do you do?
这可不妙啊
That's not good.
我和我的角色都有幽闭恐惧症
My character and I both have claustrophobia.
还有10秒钟你就要被挤爆了！
You're ten seconds away from getting crushed!
我们该肿么办才好啊？
What are we supposed to do?
从没听过
Never heard of it.
她恼羞成怒 又酩酊大醉
She's angry, she's drunk,
哦 他过来了
Oh, here he comes.
我请她喝了几杯酒
I bought her a couple of drinks,
我聪明伶俐 工作又酷
I'm smart, I've got a cool job,
不 不是的
No, it's not.
我配不上这么漂亮的
She was too beautiful for me.
我总是被得不到的女人所吸引
I'm always attracted to women I can't have.
我总是这样
I do it all the time.
我不明白
I don't understand.
好好想想
Think harder.
你离开了那个房间  发现自己
You leave the room and find yourself
怎么 有问题吗?
What, is there a problem?
没 就是挺高兴见你喝节日饮料的
No, it's nice to see you enjoying a holiday beverage.
很有圣诞风情
Pretty Christmasy.
什么时候蛋奶酒变成圣诞饮料了?
Since when is eggnog a Christmas drink?
一年到头都有鸡蛋
Eggs are available all year round.
我在游泳池边也喝这个
I've been known to enjoy this poolside.
你就是越来越有圣诞情节了
You're getting a little yuletide spirit.
一派胡言
don't be silly.
我生活在一个学术氛围很浓厚的家庭里
I grew up in a house full of crazy academics.
怪不得你这么爱圣诞节
No wonder you love Christmas.
我晓得你的论文水平
I'm familiar with your work.
我没有伤害你的意思
I didn't mean to upset you.
没事的
It's fine.
我曾经就是个看一眼就够了的女生
I'm used to being the girl who never gets looked at twice.
22岁才献出初吻
I didn't have my first kiss till I was 22,
没指望你们会理解我
I don't expect you guys to understand.
我懂
I understand.
有时  我寂寞难耐
Sometimes I get so lonely,
确实
I do.
谢谢
Thank you.
我有点喜欢她了
I'm kind of into her.
不要告诉我妈我说过这话
Don't ever tell my mother I said that.
我拿出骷髅钥匙
I take out my skeleton key
你问过我  圣诞节想要什么礼物
you asked me what I wanted for Christmas.
我好想他  想让他回到身边
I missed him and I wanted him back.
这太诡异了吧?
This is weird, right?
但你没把他带回来  是吧!
But you didn't bring him back, did you?
圣诞公公?
Santa?
我一直想和你谈谈
I've been wanting to talk to you.
抱歉让儿时的你伤心了
I'm sorry I disappointed you when you were a little boy.
我有很多魔法
I can do a lot of magical things,
我懂得
I understand.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
要是火车就好了
I hope it's a train.